Samson
You've been sweeping for half an hour
You're gonna wear a hole in the floor
Something's off
Lewes
Your in-laws are acting weird
I've been watching them all day
They keep hovering around the mixing room
And peeking through the window
Do you think they
Are jealous of you making money
And want to poison the feed
I doubt they'd poison it
But
They might
Be after my secret recipe
What
Steal the recipe
Those shameless jerks
I'll kick them out right now
Dad, calm down
We have no proof right now
If they turn the tables on us
Saying we can't tolerate the elderly
Kicking them out now
Would ruin our reputation
Then what do we do
A thief can wait a thousand days
But we can't guard for that long
Don't worry
I have a way to expose them
By the way
Don't tell Cynthia yet
I don't want her overthinking
Rest assured
They are her parents after all
Would I talk nonsense without proof